Runeshapes, inscriptions.
符形、銘文。
These are my life's work.
這些是我的畢生事業。
The more I studied, the more I began to see
隨著我的學識增長、
similar shapes in the stars above.
我也開始在群星之中看見近似的形狀。
It was then that I dedicated myself to becoming
就在那個瞬間，我下定決心成為
a Runeseeker.
一名符文探求者。
As Farrow so kindly explained, runes are very powerful and ancient inscriptions,
就如同法羅剛才解釋的那樣，符文為一種十分強大的遠古銘刻，
and they can be socketed into your items to grant them more power.
它們可以被鑲嵌至你的物品以賦予物品更強大的力量。
During the league, inscribing symbols into remnants will let you choose between
在聯盟期間，在遺物上銘刻形狀將能使你選擇
a bunch of different crafting runes that you can use to enhance your items.
數種不同的工藝符文，使你能強化你的物品。
When you come across a remnant, it has a number of slots ranging from two
當你遭遇一個遺物時，它將會擁有二至七個
to seven.
欄位。
The more slots, the more powerful the remnant encounter,
欄位越多，遺物遭遇的強度也越難，
but the more options you'll have to choose between.
但同時提供你更多的可選選項。
At the start of the game, you might find yourself
在遊戲開始時，你可能會
crafting simple damage or resistance runes
製作一些簡單的傷害或抗性符文，
that are available at a lower level
這些可於你一般來說獲得它們的等級
than you would normally be able to get them,
再更低一些時獲取，
giving you a decent power boost.
給予你可觀的強度提升。
But things quickly get more interesting.
但事情會很快的變得有趣起來。
There are 22 runes for adding or modifying runic ward,
一共有22種新增或影響符文保護的符文，
a new resource that can protect you from death.
一種會避免你死亡的全新資源。
Using these runes, you can add an extra defensive layer or turn your runic ward
使用這些符文將使你新增額外防禦面，或是將你的
into an offensive weapon using Kalguuran Runic Skills.
符文保護透過卡爾葛符文技能轉為攻擊性武器。
There are also 13 runes that add powers specific to weapon types,
同時，一共有13種會強化特定武器類型的符文，
like this one which gives a chance for grenades to explode a second time.
例如這枚使擲彈有機會二次爆炸的符文。
Or this one which gives you a new buff called Druidic Prowess
或是這枚，會在你沉重暈眩敵人時提供你一個
when heavy stunning enemies.
名為「德魯伊之賦」的全新增益。
In addition,
在此之上，
there are 22 runes designed to give you power at low levels
還有22種設計於使你在低等級時獲得強度的符文，
like this one, which gives you a bunch of elemental resistances,
例如這個，會提供你一大堆元素抗性，
or this one which gives you a ton of spirit.
又或是這個提供你一大堆精魂的。
These runes are designed to be powerful, but drop off in value as you level up.
這些符文被刻意設計的較為強大，但會隨著你升級逐漸式微。
They're great for power leveling a second character in the league.
它們將會是你在聯盟中重練時的絕佳利器。
We also have six runes that can be used to expand
我們同時有6個可在高階做裝時用於拓展
the pool of modifiers used when doing high level crafting.
可能詞綴池的符文。
So for example, you can socket Katla’s Gloom into some gloves
舉例來說，你可以鑲嵌「卡特拉的愁悵」到一些手套上
and it will enable the crafting of a bunch of new decay modifiers
其將可以被用於製作一系列的全新消逝相關詞綴，
that can be used for damage over time builds.
可用於持續傷害流派。
After socketing one of this type of rune
在鑲嵌一個此類型的符文後
use regular Exalts or Chaos orbs to try and craft the new mods.
即可使用普通的崇高或混沌石來打造新詞綴。
There are also several runes that have one off
也有一些符文會為物品提供一個強大的效果，
powerful effects on items, but are bound forever into the socket,
但會永遠被鎖定在該插槽之中，
like this one, which allows any item to gain another suffix.
例如這個，會提供任意物品一條額外後綴。
Or this one, which allows you to create a jewel socket.
或是這個，允許你創造一個珠寶插槽。
Or this series of runes
又或是這個符文系列，
that can convert any elemental mod from one element to another.
能將任意元素詞綴從一個元素轉到另一個。
There's even a rune that can upgrade any other rune,
甚至有一個可以升級其他符文的符文，
allowing you to upgrade them beyond the normal limit.
使你能將它們升級到平常無法企及的高度。
The last one I want to show you today is Aldur’s Legacy.
在今天的最後，我想為各位展示「阿德爾的傳承」。
A special rune that can be socketed into any Kalguuran or Ezomite Unique to destroy it,
它是一個特殊的符文，可以被鑲嵌於任意卡爾葛或艾茲麥傳奇物品以摧毀該物品，
but create a new rune that takes some of the properties of the unique.
並創造一個汲取了該傳奇物品部分力量的全新符文。
So for example,
舉例來說，
use this on a Trampletoe to create a Legacy of Trampletoe rune.
於「踐踏之鞋」上使用此符文以創造一個「傳承．踐踏之鞋」符文。
Socket into any boots and,
當它被鑲嵌至任意鞋子時，
just like the unique it came from,
就如同其來源的傳奇物品一般，
you’ll deal 10% of overkill damage to all enemies in a two metre radius.
你會對被擊殺敵人2公尺內的敵人造成相當於溢出傷害10%的傷害。
Or how about the Legacy of Twisted Empyrean?
又或是「傳承．畸變星穹」?
Destroy a Twisted Empyrean
摧毀一個「畸變星穹」，
and you can add cold damage based on your maximum mana to any weapon.
你將可以為任意武器新增基於最大魔力的冰冷傷害。
With Aldur’s Legacy you can create another hundred or so runes
透過「阿德爾的傳承」你可以創造另外上百多種符文，
with all sorts of unique effects.
涵蓋各式傳奇物品的效果。
At this point, you might be thinking, that's a lot of new runes
這個時候，你大概會想，真的有很多新符文耶?
and you'd be right.
而你想的沒錯。
This is the Runes of Aldur, after all.
這畢竟是「阿德爾的符文」嘛。
But we didn't want the old runes to be left behind either.
但我們也不想要舊符文就此落於下風。
A significant number of the old runes
有十分可觀的一部分沒怎麼被使用的舊符文
that were not being used are being buffed as well,
同時迎來了加強，
making this crafting system significantly better.
顯著的優化了這個工藝系統。
Explore everything runes have to offer
在台灣時間5月30號發布的「上古回歸」版本中
in the Return of the Ancients update on May 29th. See you there!
探索符文所帶來的一切可能。我們到時候見！